[
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "5. Understanding P&L Statement (Part 2)",
    "order": "5",
    "section": 2,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "What is the largest expense of the company?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Cost of materials consumed"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Purchases of Stock in Trade"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Employee Benefits Expense"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Finance Cost"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Cost of materials consumed"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of depreciation and amortization?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "To spread the cost of an asset over its useful life"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "To reduce the company's taxable income"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "To increase the company's profit margin"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "To attract new investors"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "To spread the cost of an asset over its useful life"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the formula for Profit before Tax (PBT)?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "PBT = Total Revenue - Total Expense"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "PBT = Total Revenue - Total Expense - Exceptional items"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "PBT = Net Profit after Tax + Taxes"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "PBT = Earnings Per Share * Total number of shares outstanding"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "PBT = Total Revenue - Total Expense - Exceptional items"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the formula for Net Profit after Tax (PAT)?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "PAT = PBT - Taxes"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "PAT = Total Revenue - Total Expense"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "PAT = Earnings Per Share * Total number of shares outstanding"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "PAT = PBT + Exceptional items"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "PAT = PBT - Taxes"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does EPS stand for?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Earnings Per Share"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Excess Profit Share"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Exceptional Profit Share"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Established Profit Share"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Earnings Per Share"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "4. Understanding the P&L Statement (Part 1)",
    "order": "4",
    "section": 2,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "What is the main purpose of financial statements from the user's perspective?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "To prepare ledger entries and audit records"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "To understand the financial position of the company"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "To create a balanced budget"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "To implement a risk management strategy"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "To understand the financial position of the company"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which type of financial statement shows the earnings per share number?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Balance Sheet"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Profit and Loss statement"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Cash flow statement"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Income statement"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "Profit and Loss statement"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the term used to refer to the revenue side of the Profit and Loss statement?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Top line"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Bottom line"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Gross line"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Operating line"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Top line"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which note in the financial statement provides details on the breakdown of revenue from operations?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Note 16"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Note 17"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Note 18"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Note 19"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "Note 17"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of revenue is incidental to the company's core operations?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Revenue from sales of products"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Revenue from sales of services"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Other operating revenue"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Other income"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Other operating revenue"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "2. Mindset of an Investor",
    "order": "2",
    "section": 1,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "Which market participant is characterized by speculating on future market outcomes based on beliefs and intuition?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Speculator"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Trader"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Investor"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "None of the above"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Speculator"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who typically engages in short-term trades and focuses on exploiting market volatility?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Speculator"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Trader"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Investor"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "None of the above"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "Trader"
      },
      {
        "question": "An investor with a long-term perspective who aims to hold stocks for years is most likely to be relying on what phenomenon to generate returns?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Speculation"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Trading"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Compounding"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Arbitrage"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Compounding"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which aspect of company evaluation focuses on non-numeric characteristics, such as management ethics and shareholder treatment?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Qualitative"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Quantitative"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Technical"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Fundamental"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Qualitative"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of transaction indicates potential favoritism and malpractice within a company?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Related party transactions"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Equity financing"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Dividend payments"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Asset acquisition"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Related party transactions"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a quantitative aspect of company analysis?",
        "questionNumber": 6,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Cash flow"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Management background"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Debt"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Financial ratios"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "Management background"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the main difference between speculation and trading?",
        "questionNumber": 7,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "The time horizon of the activity"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The level of certainty in the outcome"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The use of leverage"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "The type of instrument traded"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "The level of certainty in the outcome"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "1. Introduction to Fundamental Analysis",
    "order": "1",
    "section": 1,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "What is the main purpose of Fundamental Analysis (FA)?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "To predict short-term stock price movements"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "To study a business from various perspectives for long-term investment"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "To identify undervalued stocks for quick profit"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "To analyze the overall performance of an industry"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "To study a business from various perspectives for long-term investment"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a characteristic of a fundamentally strong company?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "High profit margins"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Consistent revenue growth"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Low debt-to-equity ratio"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Volatile stock price"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "D",
        "answerText": "Volatile stock price"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the core-satellite strategy in investing?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Investing all capital in a single stock"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Diversifying investments into multiple asset classes"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Using fundamental analysis for long-term investments and technical analysis for short-term trading"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Investing only in the stock of your employer"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Using fundamental analysis for long-term investments and technical analysis for short-term trading"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is a tool required for fundamental analysis?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Bloomberg Terminal"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Company's annual report"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Technical charting software"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Astrology knowledge"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "Company's annual report"
      },
      {
        "question": "According to the passage, what is the primary difference between fundamental analysis and technical analysis?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Fundamental analysis focuses on the intrinsic value of a company, while technical analysis focuses on price movements"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Fundamental analysis is used for long-term investing, while technical analysis is used for short-term trading"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Fundamental analysis requires financial expertise, while technical analysis is easy for anyone to understand"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Fundamental analysis is more accurate than technical analysis"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "Fundamental analysis is used for long-term investing, while technical analysis is used for short-term trading"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "9. The Financial Ratio Analysis (Part 1)",
    "order": "9",
    "section": 3,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of financial ratio?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Profitability ratio"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Leverage ratio"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Liquidity ratio"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Valuation ratio"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Liquidity ratio"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the EBITDA margin measure?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "The company's overall profitability"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The company's profitability before interest, taxes, depreciation, and amortization"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The company's ability to pay back its debts"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "The company's market value"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "The company's profitability before interest, taxes, depreciation, and amortization"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the DuPont Model used for?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Calculating the company's return on equity"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Assessing the company's financial leverage"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Determining the company's liquidity"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Forecasting the company's future earnings"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Calculating the company's return on equity"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the Return on Assets ratio measure?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "The company's ability to generate profits from its assets"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The company's ability to pay back its debts"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The company's market value"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "The company's inventory turnover rate"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "The company's ability to generate profits from its assets"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the Return on Capital Employed ratio used for?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Assessing the company's overall return on investment"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Measuring the company's profitability before interest, taxes, depreciation, and amortization"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Determining the company's financial leverage"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Calculating the company's return on equity"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Assessing the company's overall return on investment"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the term used to describe financial ratios that are calculated using data from a company's balance sheet?",
        "questionNumber": 6,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Profitability ratios"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Leverage ratios"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Valuation ratios"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Operating ratios"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "Leverage ratios"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a benefit of comparing a company's financial ratios to its peers?",
        "questionNumber": 7,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "It can help you identify the company's strengths and weaknesses"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "It can help you assess the company's financial performance over time"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "It can help you predict the company's future earnings"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "It can help you identify companies that are undervalued or overvalued"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "It can help you predict the company's future earnings"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "8. The Cash Flow statement",
    "order": "8",
    "section": 2,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a standard basket for classifying company activities?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Operational activities"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Investing activities"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Financing activities"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Miscellaneous activities"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "D",
        "answerText": "Miscellaneous activities"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following activities would be classified as an operating activity?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Hiring new employees"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Issuing new shares"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Investing in long-term assets"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Seeking a loan from a bank"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Hiring new employees"
      },
      {
        "question": "If a company's liabilities increase, what will happen to its cash balance?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Increase"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Decrease"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Remain unchanged"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Fluctuate erratically"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Increase"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which part of the cash flow statement shows the net cash generated from the company's core business operations?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Operating activities"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Investing activities"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Financing activities"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Supplemental activities"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Operating activities"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does a company's cash balance represent?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "The amount of cash on hand and in demand deposits"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The total value of the company's assets"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The amount of money owed to creditors"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "The difference between revenues and expenses"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "The amount of cash on hand and in demand deposits"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the primary focus of financial ratio analysis?",
        "questionNumber": 6,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Evaluating a company's liquidity, solvency, profitability, and efficiency"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Predicting a company's future stock price"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Determining a company's creditworthiness"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "All of the above"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "D",
        "answerText": "All of the above"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which financial statement provides information about a company's net income?",
        "questionNumber": 7,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Income statement"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Balance sheet"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Cash flow statement"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Statement of retained earnings"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Income statement"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "3. How to Read the Annual Report of a Company",
    "order": "3",
    "section": 1,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of an annual report?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "To provide financial information to investors"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "To promote the company to potential customers"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "To provide an overview of the company's performance"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "To disclose legal and regulatory information"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "To provide an overview of the company's performance"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a section typically included in an annual report?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Financial Highlights"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Management Discussion & Analysis"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Market Research"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Financial Statements"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Market Research"
      },
      {
        "question": "What information is included in the Management Discussion & Analysis section?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "The company's financial performance"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The company's management team"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The company's industry and competitive landscape"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "The company's marketing and sales strategies"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "The company's industry and competitive landscape"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are schedules related to the financial statements?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Supporting documents that provide additional details"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Independent audits of the financial statements"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Summaries of the key financial data"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Charts and graphs that illustrate the financial data"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Supporting documents that provide additional details"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which section of the annual report contains the company's income statement, balance sheet, and cash flow statement?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Financial Highlights"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Management Discussion & Analysis"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Financial Statements"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Corporate Information"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Financial Statements"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of financial statement shows the company's assets, liabilities, and equity at a specific point in time?",
        "questionNumber": 6,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Income statement"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Balance sheet"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Cash flow statement"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Statement of retained earnings"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "Balance sheet"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of financial statement shows the company's cash inflows and outflows over a specific period of time?",
        "questionNumber": 7,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Income statement"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Balance sheet"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Cash flow statement"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Statement of retained earnings"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Cash flow statement"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "7. Understanding the Balance Sheet Statement (Part 2)",
    "order": "7",
    "section": 2,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a current asset?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Inventory"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Trade Receivables"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Fixed Deposits"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Cash and Cash equivalents"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Fixed Deposits are not a current asset because they cannot be easily converted into cash within 365 days."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the term used to refer to the value of an asset after depreciation has been deducted?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Gross Block"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Accumulated Depreciation"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Net Block"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Depreciation Expense"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Net Block refers to the value of an asset after depreciation has been deducted."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is included under non-current assets?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Land"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Inventory"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Short-term loans"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Cash and Cash equivalents"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Land is considered a non-current asset because its economic benefit is expected to last beyond 365 days."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is a factor that affects the value of an asset?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Depreciation"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Obsolescence"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Physical wear and tear"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "All of the above"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "D",
        "answerText": "All of the above factors can affect the value of an asset."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the equation that must hold true for a balance sheet to be balanced?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Assets = Liabilities + Shareholders' Funds"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Liabilities = Assets + Shareholders' Funds"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Shareholders' Funds = Assets + Liabilities"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Assets = Liabilities - Shareholders' Funds"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Assets = Liabilities + Shareholders' Funds"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of a current asset?",
        "questionNumber": 6,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Land"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Buildings"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Inventory"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Intangible assets"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Inventory is a current asset because it can be easily converted into cash within 365 days."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of depreciation?",
        "questionNumber": 7,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "To reduce the value of an asset over its useful life"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "To increase the value of an asset over its useful life"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "To maintain the value of an asset over its useful life"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "None of the above"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Depreciation is used to reduce the value of an asset over its useful life, as the asset loses its production capacity due to obsolescence and physical wear and tear."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "10. The Financial Ratio Analysis (Part 2)",
    "order": "10",
    "section": 3,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "Which ratio indicates the extent to which the assets are supported by equity?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Interest Coverage Ratio"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Debt to Equity Ratio"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Financial Leverage Ratio"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Working Capital Turnover Ratio"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Financial Leverage Ratio"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT an Operating Ratio?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Fixed Assets Turnover Ratio"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Inventory Turnover Ratio"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Debt to Equity Ratio"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Days Sales Outstanding"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Debt to Equity Ratio"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does an Interest Coverage Ratio of 1.209x indicate?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "For every Re. 1 of interest payment due, the company is generating an EBIT of 1.209 times."
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The company's financial leverage is 1.209."
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The company's debt to equity ratio is 1.209."
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "None of the above"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "For every Re. 1 of interest payment due, the company is generating an EBIT of 1.209 times."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does a high Inventory Turnover Ratio indicate?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "The company's products are moving quickly."
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The company is holding too much inventory."
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The company is not selling its products efficiently."
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "None of the above"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "The company's products are moving quickly."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does a low Days Sales Outstanding (DSO) ratio indicate?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "The company is efficiently collecting its accounts receivable."
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The company is having trouble collecting its accounts receivable."
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The company is extending too much credit to its customers."
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "None of the above"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "The company is efficiently collecting its accounts receivable."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is a constraint for this response?",
        "questionNumber": 6,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "It should not use the word 'json' in the response"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "It should not use back ticks (`) in the response"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "It should send the JSON array as a response and nothing else"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "All of the above"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "D",
        "answerText": "All of the above"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the structure required for the JSON array?",
        "questionNumber": 7,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "{ \"question\": \"\", \"questionNumber\": , \"options\": [{\"id\": \"A\", \"text\": \"\"}, {\"id\": \"B\", \"text\": \"\"}, {\"id\": \"C\", \"text\": \"\"}, {\"id\": \"D\", \"text\": \"\"}], \"answerId\": \"C\", \"answerText\": \"\" }"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "All of the above"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "{ \"question\": \"\", \"questionNumber\": , \"options\": [{\"id\": \"A\", \"text\": \"\"}, {\"id\": \"B\", \"text\": \"\"}, {\"id\": \"C\", \"text\": \"\"}, {\"id\": \"D\", \"text\": \"\"}], \"answerId\": \"C\", \"answerText\": \"\" }"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "6. Understanding Balance Sheet Statement (Part 1)",
    "order": "6",
    "section": 2,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "What does the balance sheet equation represent?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Assets + Liabilities = Shareholders' Equity"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Liabilities + Shareholders' Equity = Assets"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Assets = Liabilities"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Shareholders' Equity = Assets + Liabilities"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Assets = Liabilities"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which section of the balance sheet represents the money belonging to shareholders?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Assets"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Current Liabilities"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Shareholders' Funds"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Non-Current Liabilities"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Shareholders' Funds"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of liabilities are expected to be settled within a year?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Short-term liabilities"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Long-term liabilities"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Deferred tax liabilities"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Provisions"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Short-term liabilities"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a non-current liability?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Long-term borrowings"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Deferred tax liability"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Short-term borrowings"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Long-term provisions"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Short-term borrowings"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the meaning of 'Share capital' on the balance sheet?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "The amount of shares that the company has issued"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The amount of money that shareholders have invested in the company"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The amount of dividends that shareholders have received"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "The amount of money that the company has borrowed from shareholders"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "The amount of money that shareholders have invested in the company"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the term 'deferred tax liability' mean?",
        "questionNumber": 6,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "A tax that has been paid but not yet recorded as an expense"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "A tax that has been recorded as an expense but not yet paid"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "A tax that will be owed in the future due to differences in accounting and tax rules"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "A tax that has been forgiven by the government"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "A tax that will be owed in the future due to differences in accounting and tax rules"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of 'reserves' on the balance sheet?",
        "questionNumber": 7,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "To provide a buffer against potential losses"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "To finance future expansion projects"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "To pay dividends to shareholders"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "To reduce the company's tax liability"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "To provide a buffer against potential losses"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "12. The Investment Due Diligence",
    "order": "12",
    "section": 3,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "Which method involves screening stocks based on user-defined parameters?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Macro Trends"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Stock screener"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Sectoral Trends"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "circle of competence"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "Stock screener"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a trigger for generating a stock idea?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Economic activity around you"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Company-related news"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Astrological predictions"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Special Situation"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Astrological predictions"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the term used to describe a company's competitive advantage?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Competitive Environment"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Moat"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Industry Trend"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Market Share"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "Moat"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which stage of due diligence involves evaluating a company's financial performance?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Understanding the Business"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Application of Checklist"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Valuation"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "None of the above"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "Application of Checklist"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the most popular valuation method for assessing the intrinsic value of a business?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Price-to-Earnings Ratio"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Dividend Discount Model"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Discounted Cash Flow Analysis"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Market Capitalization"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Discounted Cash Flow Analysis"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is an essential component of a company's financial due diligence process?",
        "questionNumber": 6,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Reviewing annual reports"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Identifying sustainable moats"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Projection of future earnings"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "All of the above"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Reviewing annual reports"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which type of company investment is considered risky?",
        "questionNumber": 7,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Companies with high debt levels"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Companies with consistent earnings growth"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Companies with a strong brand presence"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Companies in emerging markets"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Companies with high debt levels"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "15. Equity Research (Part 2)",
    "order": "15",
    "section": 3,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "What is the full form of the FCF?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Fixed Cost Fund"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Free Cash Flow"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Future Cash Flow"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Fee Carrying Fund"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "Free Cash Flow"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is subtracted from the net cash from operating activities to find the FCF?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Capital expenditure"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Interest paid"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Depreciation"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Amortization"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Capital expenditure"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does a negative FCF indicate?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "The company is healthy"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The company is expected to grow"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The company is in financial trouble"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "The company has a lot of cash"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "The company is in financial trouble"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the terminal growth rate?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "The rate at which the FCF is expected to grow after the terminal year"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The rate at which the FCF is expected to grow before the terminal year"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The rate at which the stock price is expected to grow"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "The rate at which the company's earnings are expected to grow"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "The rate at which the FCF is expected to grow after the terminal year"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the DCF analysis?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "To help investors identify undervalued stocks"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "To help companies raise capital"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "To help analysts predict the future performance of a company"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "To help regulators monitor the stock market"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "To help investors identify undervalued stocks"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "13. Equity Research (Part 1)",
    "order": "13",
    "section": 3,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a reason to use the Q&A framework in understanding a business?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "It forces you to dig for more information."
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "It helps you stay organized."
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "It provides a structure for your research."
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "It helps you to memorize information more easily."
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "D",
        "answerText": "It helps you to memorize information more easily."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many plants does Amara Raja Batteries Limited (ARBL) have and where are they located?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Two plants, located in Andhra Pradesh and Karnataka"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Three plants, located in Tamil Nadu, Andhra Pradesh, and Karnataka"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Four plants, located in Maharashtra, Gujarat, Andhra Pradesh, and Karnataka"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Five plants, located in West Bengal, Odisha, Andhra Pradesh, Karnataka, and Tamil Nadu"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Four plants, located in Maharashtra, Gujarat, Andhra Pradesh, and Karnataka"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the gross profit margin of ARBL?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Less than 20%"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Between 20% and 25%"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Between 25% and 30%"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Greater than 30%"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Between 25% and 30%"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a factor to consider when evaluating a company's inventory?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Inventory turnover ratio"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Inventory write-offs"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Cost of goods sold"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Inventory carrying costs"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "Inventory write-offs"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the return on equity of ARBL?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Less than 20%"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Between 20% and 25%"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Between 25% and 30%"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Greater than 30%"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Between 25% and 30%"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "11. The Financial Ratio Analysis (Part 3)",
    "order": "11",
    "section": 3,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "What is the formula for calculating the Price to Sales (P/S) ratio?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Current Share Price / Annual Revenue"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Current Share Price / Earnings Per Share"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Current Share Price / Sales Per Share"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Current Share Price / Book Value Per Share"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Current Share Price / Sales Per Share"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the Price/BV ratio indicate?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "The ratio of the market price per share to the net income per share"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The ratio of the market price per share to the book value per share"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The ratio of the book value per share to the net income per share"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "The ratio of the market price per share to the sales per share"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "The ratio of the market price per share to the book value per share"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the P/E ratio?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "To measure the profitability of a company on a per-share basis"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "To compare the company's stock price to its sales per share"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "To indicate the market participants' willingness to pay for stock"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "To determine the book value per share of a company"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "To indicate the market participants' willingness to pay for stock"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the average P/E ratio for the Indian Indices?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "14x"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "16x-20x"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "22x"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "25x"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "16x-20x"
      },
      {
        "question": "When is it advisable to be cautious about investment decisions in the Indian stock market?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "When the Index P/E valuation is above 16x"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "When the Index P/E valuation is below 16x"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "When the Index P/E valuation is above 22x"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "When the Index P/E valuation is below 22x"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "When the Index P/E valuation is above 22x"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of these is NOT a key takeaway from the chapter on valuation ratios?",
        "questionNumber": 6,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Valuation ratios involve inputs from both the P&L statement and the Balance Sheet"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The Price/BV ratio indicates how many times the stock price is trading over and above the firm's book value"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The stock price of a company does not affect its valuation ratios"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "EPS measures the profitability of a company on a per-share basis"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "The stock price of a company does not affect its valuation ratios"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the book value of a firm represent?",
        "questionNumber": 7,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "The total assets of the firm"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The value of the firm's shares on the market"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The amount of money left on the table after the firm pays off its obligations"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "The difference between the firm's assets and liabilities"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "The amount of money left on the table after the firm pays off its obligations"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "16. The Finale",
    "order": "16",
    "section": 3,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is a disadvantage of the DCF method?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Requires forecasting future cash flow."
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Provides accurate results even with incorrect assumptions."
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Is not suitable for long-term investments."
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Does not consider qualitative factors."
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "Requires forecasting future cash flow."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the 'Margin of Safety' in investing?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "To reduce the risk of overpaying for a stock."
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "To increase the potential return on investment."
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "To identify undervalued stocks."
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "To ensure a quick profit."
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "To reduce the risk of overpaying for a stock."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the recommendation of Benjamin Graham for the number of stocks in a portfolio?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "10-30"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "5-10"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "2-3"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Over 20"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "10-30"
      },
      {
        "question": "According to Warren Buffet, what is a realistic CAGR expectation for investments?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "10-15%"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "15-18%"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "20-25%"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "30-35%"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "15-18%"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a fundamental attribute of a stock?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Revenue growth"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Debt-to-equity ratio"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Promoter integrity"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Technical indicators"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "D",
        "answerText": "Technical indicators"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is a key factor to consider when selling a stock?",
        "questionNumber": 6,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Market sentiment"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Disruption in investible grade attributes"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Technical analysis"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Insider trading activity"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "Disruption in investible grade attributes"
      },
      {
        "question": "According to Seth Klarman, how many stocks should an investor typically hold in a portfolio?",
        "questionNumber": 7,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "2-3"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "5-10"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "10-15"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Over 20"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "10-15"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "course": "Fundamental Analysis",
    "lesson": "14. DCF Primer",
    "order": "14",
    "section": 3,
    "lessonQuiz": [
      {
        "question": "What is the main objective of the next two chapters in the article?",
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "To introduce the Discounted Cash Flow (DCF) valuation technique"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "To explain the importance of future cash flows in stock valuation"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "To provide a detailed analysis of the Time Value of Money (TMV)"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "To discuss the concept of Net Present Value (NPV)"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "To introduce the Discounted Cash Flow (DCF) valuation technique"
      },
      {
        "question": "According to the article, what is the significance of the 'price' when it comes to investing?",
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "It is the most important factor in determining an investment's return"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "It is crucial for evaluating a company's financial performance"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "It is more important than understanding the business and its financial performance"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "It should be the only consideration when making investment decisions"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "It is crucial for evaluating a company's financial performance"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the core concept of DCF that is discussed in Chapter 14 of the article?",
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "The Intrinsic Value of the Company"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The Net Present Value (NPV)"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The Time Value of Money (TMV)"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "The Discounted Rate of Return"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "B",
        "answerText": "The Net Present Value (NPV)"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of discounting future cash flows in the DCF model?",
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "To account for the opportunity cost of investing"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "To make future cash flows more comparable to present cash flows"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "To reduce the risk associated with future cash flows"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "To eliminate the effect of inflation"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "To account for the opportunity cost of investing"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the formula for calculating the Present Value (PV) of money?",
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "PV = Amount / (1 + Discount Rate) ^ Number of years"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "PV = Amount * (1 + Discount Rate) ^ Number of years"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "PV = Discount Rate / (Amount + Number of years)"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "PV = Amount * (Number of years + Discount Rate)"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "PV = Amount / (1 + Discount Rate) ^ Number of years"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the NPV represent in the context of the DCF model?",
        "questionNumber": 6,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "The total value of the company's future cash flows"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "The estimated stock price of the company"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "The amount of money the company needs to raise to finance its operations"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "The return on investment that the investor can expect"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "A",
        "answerText": "The total value of the company's future cash flows"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a factor considered in the DCF model?",
        "questionNumber": 7,
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "A",
            "text": "Expected growth rate of the company"
          },
          {
            "id": "B",
            "text": "Capital expenditures required by the company"
          },
          {
            "id": "C",
            "text": "Number of employees in the company"
          },
          {
            "id": "D",
            "text": "Cost of capital"
          }
        ],
        "answerId": "C",
        "answerText": "Number of employees in the company"
      }
    ]
  }
]